Undergraduate Alumni Records, 18th Century 1748-1799: Preliminary Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 1: Alumni Files, 1748-1799; 1382 files
  - Patterson, Thomas, 1783; portion of 1 box (Box 42)
  - Radcliff (Radclift), Jacob, 1783; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 42)
  - Riddle, Joseph, 1783; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 42)
  - Rock, James, 1783; portion of 1 box (Box 42)
  - Roosevelt, Martin, 1783; portion of 1 box (Box 42)
  - Snowden, Gilbert Tennent, 1783; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 42)
  - Taylor, Edward, 1783; portion of 1 box (Box 42)
  - Venable, Joseph, 1783; portion of 1 box (Box 42)
  - Wood, John Thornton, 1783; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 42)
  - Woodford, John Thornton, 1783; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Woodruff, George Whitefield, 1783; portion of 1 box (Box 42)
  - Baldwin, John, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 42)
  - Baldwin, Mathew, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 42)
  - Bayard, James Ashton, 1784; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 42)
  - Bayard, Samuel, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 42)
  - Campfield, William, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 42)
  - Clay, Joseph, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 42)
  - Condict, Ira, 1784; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 42)
  - Cooper, Thomas, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 42)
  - Edwards, Alexander, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 42)
  - Ford, Gabriel H., 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 42)
  - Forman, Agur T., 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - Gibbes, John, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - Hopkins, James, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - Johnston, Abel, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - Livingston, Peter Robert, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - Livingston, Robert LeRoy, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - McWhorter, Alexander Cumming, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - Morris, James, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - Ogden, Isaac, 1784; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 43)
  - Penn, James, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - Radcliff, William, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - Shaw, Leonard D., 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - Spencer, John Eaton, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - Squier, Zadoc, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - Tenbroeck, Abraham, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - Woodruff, Abner, 1784; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - Cazier, John L., 1785; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Cazier, Matthias, 1785; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - Greene, George Washington, 1785; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Harper, Robert Goodloe, 1785; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 43)
  - Henry, John Vernor, 1785; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - Ker, Oliver L., 1785; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - McCoy, James, 1785; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - Smith, Richard, 1785; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - Smith, Samuel, Jr., 1785; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Snowden, Isaac, 1785; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - St. C. (Clair?), unknown, 1785; portion of 1 box (Box 43)
  - Tappan, John, 1785; portion of 1 box (Box 44)
  - Thompson, James, 1785; portion of 1 box (Box 44)
  - Whaley, Hercules, 1785; portion of 1 box (Box 44)
  - Wilkin, James Whitney, 1785; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 44)
  - Banaker, Abraham C., 1786; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Banker, Abraham, 1786; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Broome, Samuel Platt, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 44)
  - Brown, William Maxwell, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 44)
  - Clymer, Henry, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 44)
  - Coleman, Henry Embry, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 44)
  - Forman, William Gordon, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 44)
  - Graham, Edward, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 44)
  - Grant, Thomas, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 44)
  - Howe, Nathaniel, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 44)
  - Hugg, William King, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 44)
  - Hunt, Ralph P., 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 44)
  - Hunt, William Pitt, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 44)
  - Imlay, James Henderson, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Edward, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 44)
  - King, Richard Hugg, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 44)
  - Livingston, Maturin, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 44)
  - Livingston, Peter William, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 44)
  - Marsh, Amos, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 45)
  - Mosby, Richard, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 45)
  - Nicoll, Abimael Youngs, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 45)
  - Pollock, Thomas, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 45)
  - Smalley, Henry, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 45)
  - Smith, Charles, 1786; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 45)
  - Smith, Samuel, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 45)
  - Snowden, Samuel Finley, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 45)
  - Stewart, Samuel Robert, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 45)
  - Toomer, Anthony, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 45)
  - Vancleve, John Wright, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 45)
  - Vergereau, John C., 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 45)
  - Vergraw, John C., 1786; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Wallace, William, 1786; portion of 1 box (Box 45)
  - Abeel, John Neilson, 1787; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 45)
  - Alexander, Evan Shelby, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 45)
  - Blanchard, Isaac, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 45)
  - Brooks, unknown, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 45)
  - Camp, Jabez, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 45)
  - Clymer, Meredith, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 45)
  - Crow, George, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 46)
  - Duff, Thomas, Jr., 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 46)
  - Finley, Robert, 1787; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 46)
  - Gibson, James, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 46)
  - Green, Charles Dickinson, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 46)
  - Harris, Samuel, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 46)
  - Higginson, Nathaniel, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 46)
  - Hughes, Robert, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 46)
  - Irwin, James, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 46)
  - James, William D., 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 46)
  - Jones, Cantwell, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 46)
  - Meade, David, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 46)
  - Perrine, Matthew La Rue, 1787; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 46)
  - Pollock, George, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 46)
  - Ramsay, John, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 46)
  - Rattoone, Elijah Dunham, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 46)
  - Read, James Bond, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 46)
  - Read, John, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 46)
  - Smith, Daniel, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 47)
  - Smith, John R., 1787; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 47)
  - Snowden, Isaac, 1787; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Snowden, Nathaniel Randolph, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 47)
  - Stockton, Lucius Horatio, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 47)
  - Thew, Daniel, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 47)
  - Weir, James, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 47)
  - Woolsey, Jeremiah, 1787; portion of 1 box (Box 47)
  - Bellach, Thomas H., 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 47)
  - Clarkson, George, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 47)
  - Condict, Aaron, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 47)
  - Dill, Armstrong, 1788; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Drury, Edmund, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 47)
  - Eppes, Richard, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 47)
  - Forster, Samuel, 1788; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Foster, Samuel Blair, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 47)
  - Green, John Wickliffe, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 47)
  - Harris, Thomas R., 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 47)
  - Henderson, Matthew, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 47)
  - Henderson, Matthew, 1788; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Holmes, Allen S., 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 47)
  - Howell, Nathaniel Woodhull, 1788; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 47)
  - Joomar, Anthon, 1788; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Kirkpatrick, William, 1788; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 47)
  - Lewis, William, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 47)
  - Livingston, Peter Schuyler, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 47)
  - Livingston, unknown, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 47)
  - Marshall, William, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 48)
  - McMillan, Ephraim, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 48)
  - Murray, John, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 48)
  - Randolph, Richard, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 48)
  - Smith, Samuel, 1788; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Smith, Timothy Treadwell, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 48)
  - Stone, David, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 48)
  - Taliaferro, John, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 48)
  - Tennant, John, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 48)
  - Thompson, Smith, 1788; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 48)
  - VanDyke, Nicholas Jr., 1788; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 48)
  - Wells, John, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 48)
  - Wiley, David, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 48)
  - Wilson, Samuel, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 48)
  - Wootton, Turner, 1788; portion of 1 box (Box 48)
  - Anderson, William A., 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 48)
  - Blackledge, William, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 48)
  - Blount, Willie, 1789; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 48)
  - Boileau, Nathaniel Britton, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 49)
  - Chapman, Robert Hett, 1789; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 49)
  - Collins, John, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 49)
  - Cook, Henry, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 49)
  - Crane, Isaac Watts, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 49)
  - Darrell, Edward, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 49)
  - Deas, David, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 49)
  - Deas, Henry, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 49)
  - DeWint, Christian, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 49)
  - Dickerson, Mahlon, 1789; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 49)
  - Donaldson, Thomas, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 49)
  - English, David, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 49)
  - Freeman, James, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 49)
  - Gardiner, David, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 49)
  - Gardiner, John Lyon, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 49)
  - Heriot, John, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 49)
  - Hosack, David, 1789; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 49)
  - Huger, Daniel, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Hutchins, Thomas, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Irving, Thomas Pitt, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Irwin, John, 1789; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Jennings, Henry, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - McClenachan, George, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Morgan, John, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Perry, William, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Pierson, Isaac, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Smith, William S., 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Snowden, Charles Jeffry, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Stevens, O'Neal, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - White Eyes, George Morgan, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Whiteyes, George, 1789; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Wilson, Ephraim King, 1789; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Wood, Silas, 1789; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. Contains oversize material. (Box 50)
  - Alston, Samuel, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Bell, Daniel, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Champ, Jabez, 1790; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Churchill, Armstead, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Clarkson, ?, 1790; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Clarkson, Gerard, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Colcock, Charles, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Gibbes, Lewis, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Gibbes, Thomas Stanyarne, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Gibbons, Barach, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Gibbons, Joseph, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Hanna, William, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Harris, Israel, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 50)
  - Harvey, Augustus William, 1790; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 50)
  - Hollingsworth, John, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 51)
  - Howe, William, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 51)
  - Huger, David, 1790; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Hutchins, Henry, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 51)
  - Johnson, Robert Gibbon, 1790; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 51)
  - Johnson, William, Jr., 1790; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 51)
  - Lott, Ralph Phillips, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 51)
  - Matthews, William, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 51)
  - McWhorter, John, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 51)
  - Morell, Brian, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 51)
  - Perkins, Ezekiel, 1790; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Pickens, Ezekiel, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 51)
  - Purdie, John, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 51)
  - Ramsey, John, 1790; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Reed, John, 1790; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Ruan, John, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 51)
  - Smith, Jacob, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 51)
  - Steele, Isaac, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 51)
  - Taylor, John, 1790; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 51)
  - Thompson, John, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 51)
  - Timothy, Benjamin Franklin, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 51)
  - Woodhull, George Spafford, 1790; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 51)
  - Young, Thomas, 1790; portion of 1 box (Box 51)
  - Barclay, David, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 51)
  - Bayard, ?, 1791; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Bleecker, John Rutger, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 51)
  - Boardly, William, 1791; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Bordley, William, 1791; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 51)
  - Bowie, Thomas Contee, 1791; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 51)
  - Burnet, Jacob, 1791; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 51)
  - Caldwell, Joseph, Jr., 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Callaway, Henry, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Callaway, Robert, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Cambell, ?, 1791; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Campbell, James, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Campbell, William, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Dennis, John, 1791; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 52)
  - Dickenson, Samuel, 1791; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Dickerson(Dickinson), Samuel Sharpe, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Dickinson, John, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Duckett, Allen Bowie, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Edmondson, John, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Ferguson, William, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Gale, Robert, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Gelston, Maltby, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Harwood, Richard, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Hayward, Thomas, 1791; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 52)
  - Henry, George, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Henry, Samuel, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Hollyday, Henry, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Hutchins, Isaac, 1791; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Johnes, Alexander, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Jones, Alexander, 1791; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Lewis, Stephen J., 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Lott, Ralph, 1791; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Marchant, Peter, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Markoe, Francis, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Markoe, Peter, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Maxwell, John Berrian, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - McCrady, John, 1791; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - McCready, John, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Mercer, Boyd, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Merchant, Peter, 1791; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Nicholson, James, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 52)
  - Noble, John, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 53)
  - Pierson, Ebenezer Howell, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 53)
  - Purcell, Henry, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 53)
  - Randolph, John, 1791; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 53)
  - Randolph, Theodorick B., 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 53)
  - Rea, ?, 1791; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Rhea, Ebenezer, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 53)
  - Roosevelt, James Christopher, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 53)
  - Ross, ?, 1791; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Ross, Charles, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 53)
  - Steel, Jacob, 1791; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Steele, Isaac, 1791; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Stephens, Oneal G., 1791; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Stockton, Job, 1791; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Stone, Frederick, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 53)
  - Sullivan, James, 1791; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Sullivan, John, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 53)
  - Taylor, Jesse, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 53)
  - Van Arsdale, Elias, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 53)
  - Watkins, William Morton, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 53)
  - Wayne, Isaac, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 53)
  - Wayne, Isaac, 1791; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Wayne, Stephen, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 53)
  - Wright, Thomas, 1791; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 53)
  - Wykoff, Peter, 1791; portion of 1 box (Box 53)
  - Alexander, Joseph McKnitt, Jr., 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 53)
  - Bayard, Nicholas, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 53)
  - Bayley, James P., 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 53)
  - Bayley, James P., 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 51)
  - Bibb, George M., 1792; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. Contains oversize material. (Box 53)
  - Bleecker, Peter, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 54)
  - Burnet, George Whitefield, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 54)
  - Chesnut, James, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 54)
  - Chetwood, William, 1792; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 54)
  - Cole, ?, 1792; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Corbon, ?, 1792; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Coxe, Alexander, 1792; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Deas, Robert, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 54)
  - Early, Peter, 1792; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 54)
  - Ford, Jacob, Jr., 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 54)
  - Harris, Charles Wilson, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 54)
  - Heriot, Robert, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 54)
  - Hodgedon, Benjamin, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 54)
  - Hosack, William, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 54)
  - Hughes, Samuel, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 54)
  - Hutchins, Henry, 1792; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Jones, ?, 1792; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Lee, Edmund Jennings, 1792; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 54)
  - Leech, George M., 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 54)
  - Logan, Joseph, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 54)
  - Long, J.J., 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - Maxwell, George Clifford, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - McCree, David, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - Milnor, Joseph Kirkbride, 1792; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 55)
  - Morton, George Washington, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - Otto, John Conrad, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - Pierie, William, 1792; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Pintard, Lewis Smith, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - Reed, Joseph, Jr., 1792; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 55)
  - Ross, James D., 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - Ross, William, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - Ruan, James, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - Russell, Robert, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - Ryers, John Pelion, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - Sayres, John Johnson, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - Sloan, John, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - Sloan, William B., 1792; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 55)
  - Snowden, William, 1792; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Steele, Henry, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - Stockton, Job, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - Ten Eyck, Jacob, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - Thompson, Jacob S., 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - Thompson, John, 1792; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Watkins, William Morton, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - White, Alexander, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - Willing, George, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - Wykoff, Henry, 1792; portion of 1 box (Box 55)
  - Archer, unknown, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Bonney, Joseph, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Chamberlain, Robins, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Coles, Walter, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Conrad, Edward, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Ditmars, Dow, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Eyre, Manuel, Jr., 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Field, Robert, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Gibson, John, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Hobart, John Henry, 1793; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 56)
  - Huger, Jacob, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Hunt, Nathaniel, Jr., 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Hunt, Robert, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Jordan, ?, 1793; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Jordan, John, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Litter, ?, 1793; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Maia, ?, 1793; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Maxwell, Stephen, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - McCrea, ?, 1793; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - McKee, David, 1793; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Nandorne, ?, 1793; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Neilson, John, 1793; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 56)
  - Ogden, Robert, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Ogden, Robert, 1793; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Roat, William, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Skinner, Abraham, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Smith, Enoch, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Snowden, ?, 1793; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Staples, John, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Steel, ?, 1793; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Stelle, James T., 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Stewart, Alexander, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Taylor, Bennett, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Tennent, Charles, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Terhune, John, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 56)
  - Van Doren, Isaac, 1793; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 57)
  - Wallace, Joshua Maddox, 1793; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 57)
  - Willing, Richard, 1793; portion of 1 box (Box 57)
  - Bay, William, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 57)
  - Bayly, Thomas Monteagle, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 57)
  - Broom, James M., 1794; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 57)
  - Caldwell, Andrew, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 57)
  - Campbell, George Washington, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 57)
  - Corbin, James R., 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 57)
  - Cresap, James E., 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 57)
  - Dayton, Horatio, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 57)
  - Dickson, John M., 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 57)
  - Elmendorf, Edmund, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 57)
  - Everett, Nicholas C., 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 57)
  - Ewing, William Belford, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 57)
  - Force, James Gildersleeve, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 57)
  - Furman, John White, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 57)
  - Furman, Moore, Jr., 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 57)
  - Gibbes, ?, 1794; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Gibbs, Isaac, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 57)
  - Gibbs, Stephen, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 57)
  - Gibson, ?, 1794; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Gibson, Andrew, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 57)
  - Green, Richard Montgomery, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 57)
  - Henry, ?, 1794; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)